Schein, Donald; Papers apap209
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 January (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 February (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 March (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 April (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 May (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 June (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 July (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 August (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 September (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 October (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1985, Day-Timer, 1985 November (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 November (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 December (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1985, Development (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1985, EITV (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1985, Endowment Committee (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1985, Engineering Department (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1985, Environmental Clearinghouse of Schenectady (ECOS) (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1985, Fiscal Fitness, WMHT Production, Transcript (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1985, Instructional Television Fixed Service (ITFS) (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1985, Journal (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
  (includes inserts).
- 1985, KCSD, Kansas City, Information Packet (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1985, KUHT (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1985, Land Mobile Uplink, 1985-1986 (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1985, Legislation Affecting Public Broadcasting, 1985-1986 (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1985, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1985, News Service (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1985, Nielsen Ratings (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1985, NTIA Grant Proposal (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1985, PBS Anti-Clutter Survey (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1985, PBS National Advertising Plan, 1985-1986 (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31)
- 1985, PBS Program Duplication Policies (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32)
- 1985, Public Broadcasting (Box 26 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 33-39)
- 1985, Public Broadcasting (Box 27 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1-9)
- 1985, The Public Broadcasting Report, Periodical (Box 27 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1985, Public Citizen, Periodical (Box 27 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1985, RPI Course in Technical Writing (Box 27 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1985, Satellite Uplink (Box 27 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13-15)
- 1985, Satellite Uplink, NTIA Endorsement (Box 27 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1985, SCC Human Relations Seminar (Box 27 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1985, "Sharing Savings" Bonus (Box 27 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1985, Staff Directories, 1985-1991 (Box 27 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1985, Television/Broadcast Communications, Periodical (Box 27 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1985, Williams, Bon, Computer Consultant (Box 27 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1985, WMHT, Program (Box 27 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22-23)
- 1985, WMHT Capital Planning Schedule (Box 27 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1985, WMHT Internal Records (Box 27 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25-27)
- 1985, WMHT Internal Records (Box 28 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1-8)
- 1986, A Tribal Memory of Public Broadcasting, CPB Report (Box 28 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1986, Auction (Box 28 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1986, Board of Trustees (Box 28 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11-12)
- 1986, Boy Scout Explorers, 1986-1987 (Box 28 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1986, Capital Drive (Box 28 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1986, Capital Fund Drive Consultants (Box 28 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15-16)
- 1986, Capital Region, Program (Box 28 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17-20)
- 1986, Chain of Command (Box 28 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1986, Channels (Box 28 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1986, Computer System (Box 28 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1986, Corporation for Public Broadcasting (CPB) Directory (Box 28 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1986, CPB Seminar on Management Strategy (Box 28 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1986, Current (Periodical) (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1-3)
- 1986, Current Publishing Committee (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1986, Daily Calendar, 1986 January-1986 July (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1986, Daily Calendar, 1986 August-1986 September (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1986, Daily Calendar, 1986 October-1987 January (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 January (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 February (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 March (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 April (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 May (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 June (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 July (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 August (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 September (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 October (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1986, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1986 November (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1986, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1986 December (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1986, Development Committee (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1986, Division Heads (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1986, Eastern Educational Television Network (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1986, Eastern Educational Television Network (EEN) Board Meeting, 1986 September 14-1986 September 16 (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1986, Eastern Educational Television Network Board of Trustees Meeting, 1986 September 15 (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1986, EITV (periodical) (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1986, Endowment Committee (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1986, Faces of the City, Program, 1986-1987 (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1986, Governance & Management Handbook for Public Broadcasting (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1986, General Manager Search Committee (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1986, Grimmer, Jean, Pending Memoranda (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30-31)
- 1986, Instructional Television (ITV) (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32-34)
- 1986, Journal (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 35)
- 1986, Life Insurance (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 36)
- 1986, Mid-Hudson FM Transmitter (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 37)
- 1986, "Must Carry" Legislation (Box 29 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 38)
- 1986, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 30 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1986, New York Network (Box 30 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1986, Nominating Committee (Box 30 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1986, NTIA Grant Application (Box 30 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1986, PBS Home Video Service (Box 30 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1986, PBS Marketing Seminar (Box 30 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1986, PBS Programming Pipeline (Box 30 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1986, PBS Selects (Home Video Service) (Box 30 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1986, Poughkeepsie Transmitter, 1986-1987 (Box 30 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1986, Project Development Proposals (Box 30 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1986, Public Broadcasting (Box 30 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11-25)
- 1986, Public Relations Director Search Committee (Box 30 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1986, Public Relations Director Search Committee (Box 31 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1986, RISE-ing Stars (Telethon) (Box 31 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1986, Search Committee (Box 31 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1986, Spector, Beryl -- Memorial (Box 31 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1986, Standard Operating Procedure Manual [Draft?] (Box 31 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1986, Strategic Planning for PBS: A Report To PBS Member Stations (Box 31 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1986, Tangarone, Tony -- Pending Memoranda (Box 31 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7-8)
- 1986, Union Negotiations (Box 31 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1986, VHF Drop -- In (Box 31 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1986, Williams, Robert -- Computer Installation (Box 31 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1986, Wine Tasting (Box 31 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1986, WMHT Internal Records (Box 31 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13-26)
- 1986, WMHT Internal Records (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1-4)
- 1986, WMHT-FM Internal Records (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1986, WMHT -- Report on Health Insurance Plan (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1986, WMHT Trustee's Manual (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1986, WWCN Prospective Purchase, 1986-1987 (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1987, Board of Trustees (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1987, By-Laws Committee (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1987, Capital Fund Drive (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1987, Capital Region (Program) (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12-14)
- 1987, Capital Region Magazine -- Notes and Memoranda (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1987, Conferences (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1987, Correspondence (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1987, Current (Periodical) (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18-22)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 January (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 February (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 March (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 April (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 May (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 June (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 July (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 August (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 September (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 October (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 November (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 33)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 December (Box 32 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 34)
- 1987, Fact Finders WMHT Opinion Survey (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1987, Journal (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1987, WUSV Purchase Proposal (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1987, Kingston FM Translator (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1987, Local Programming (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1987, National Association of Public Television Stations (NAPTS) St. Louis Convention (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1987, New Paltz FM Transmitter (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1987, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1987, Petersburgh Property (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1987, Proctor's Theatre Development Fund Brochures (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1987, Public Broadcasting (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11-19)
- 1987, Quiet Campaign Testimonial Letters (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1987, Report of the PBS Special Committee on Program Policies and Procedures (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1987, Retirement (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22-24)
- 1987, Ricotta, Kitty (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1987, Soviet Satellite Project (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1987, WMHT Financial Statements (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1987, WMHT Internal Records (Box 33 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28-34)
- 1987, WMHT Internal Records (Box 34 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1-4)
- 1987, WMHT Internal Records and News Clippings (Box 34 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1987, WMHT Internal Records and News Clippings, 1987 May-1987 June (Box 34 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1987, WMHT Internal Records and News Clippings, 1987 June (Box 34 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1987, WMHT Internal Records and News Clippings, 1987 July (Box 34 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1987, WMHT Internal Records and News Clippings, 1987 July-1987 August (Box 34 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9-10)
- 1987, WMHT Trustee's Manual (Box 34 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1987, WMHT 25th Anniversary Celebration (Box 34 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1987, WMHT 25th Anniversary Program (Box 34 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1987, WMHT Video Recollections (Box 34 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1987, WMHT Video Recollections -- Interviews Transcripts (Box 34 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15-17)
- 1988, Capital Region (Program) (Box 34 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18-21)
- 1988, Current (Periodical) (Box 34 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22-24)
- 1988, Daily Calendar, 1988 January-1988 February (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 March (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 April (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 June (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 July (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 August (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 September (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 October (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 November (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 December (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1988, Donald Schein Testimonial Dinner, 04/14/1988 (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1988, Donald Schein Tribute Dinner, 04/14/1988 (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1988, Donald Schein Tribute Dinner -- Guestbook, 04/14/1988 (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1988, Johanson, Patricia (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1988, Journal (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1988, Missouri Travel Guide (Publication) (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1988, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1988, Proctor's (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1988, Proctor's, 1988-1995 (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1988, Proctor's Steering Committee (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1988, Public Broadcasting (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1988, Public Broadcasting (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1988, The Public Broadcasting Report (periodical) (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1988, Russia Trip (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1988, WMHT Internal Records (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25-27)
- 1989, Alumni Giving (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1989, Capital (Program) (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29-31)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 January (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 February (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 33)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 March (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 34)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 April (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 35)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 May (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 36)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 June (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 37)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 July (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 38)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 August (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 39)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 September (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 40)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 October (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 41)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 November (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 42)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 December (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 43)
- 1989, Environmental Clearinghouse of Schenectady (ECOS) (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 44)
- 1989, Fundraising, 1989-1991 (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 45)
- 1989, Journal (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 46)
- 1989, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 47)
- 1989, Proctor's (Box 35 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 48-50)
- 1989, Public Broadcasting (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1989, WMHT Internal Records (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2-3)
- 1990, Capital (Program) (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4-6)
- 1990, Current (Periodical) (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 January (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 February (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 March (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 April (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 May (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 June (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 July (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 August (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 September (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 October (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 November (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 December (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1990, Journal (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1990, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1990, Proctor's (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1990, Public Broadcasting (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1990, Travel Master Recreational Vehicle (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1990, WMHT Internal Records (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1991, Comint (Periodical) (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1991, Current (Periodical) (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1991, Friedman, Howard (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1991, News Clippings, General (Newsprint) (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1991, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1991, News Clippings on WMHT, Newsprint (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31)
- 1991, Proctor's Theater Guild (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32)
- 1991, Program Guide/Prelude (Program) (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 33)
- 1991, Public Broadcasting (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 34)
- 1991, WMHT Internal Records (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 35-36)
- 1991, WMHT Production Services Packet (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 37)
- 1992, Comint (Periodical) (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 38)
- 1992, Correspondence (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 39)
- 1992, Correspondence with Legislators and Related Material, 1992-1993 (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 40)
- 1992, Current (Periodical) (Box 36 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 41-43)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 January (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 February (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 March (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 April (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 May (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 June (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 July (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 August (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 September (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 October (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 November (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 December (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1992, Journal (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1992, News Clippings on Broadcasting (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1992, News Clippings, General (Newsprint) (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1992, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1992, Prelude (Program) (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1992, Public Broadcasting (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1992, WMHT Internal Records (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19-20)
- 1992, WMHT Station Histories, 1953-1992 (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1993, Comint (Periodical), Autumn 1993 (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1993, Current (Periodical) (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23-26)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 January (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 February (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 March (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 April (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 May (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 June (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 July (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 33)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 August (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 34)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 September (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 35)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 October (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 36)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 November (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 37)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 December (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 38)
- 1993, Journal (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 39)
- 1993, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 40)
- 1993, Prelude, Program (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 41)
- 1993, Public Broadcasting (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 42)
- 1993, WMHT Internal Records (Box 37 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 43)
- 1994, Current (Periodical) (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1994, Day-Timer, 1994 January (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1994, Day-Timer, 1994 February (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1994, Day-Timer, 1994 March (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1994, Day-Timer, 1994 April (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1994, Day-Timer, 1994 May (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1994, Day-Timer, 1994 June (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1994, Day-Timer, 1994 July (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1994, Journal (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1994, Journal (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1994, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1994, Prelude (Program) (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1994, Public Broadcasting (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)